<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<sessions>

<session>
<prompt>
Write a story using the following prompt: A well-intentioned medical policy slowly erodes personal bodily autonomy.
</prompt>
<submit>
The organ donation system moved from opt-in to opt-out, from affirmative consent to presumed consent.

It was the toxins in the air and the water, which were hard on the internal organs, seeing people die before their time. The idea that you should have some say about what happens to your body after death began to seem quaint, when so many people were in such great need.

And of course that wasn't the end of it, because eventually, they stopped letting you opt out entirely. There was no question of the consent of the dead, it seemed silly to care about what a dead man might want done with his body, to even allow the possibility that someone might throw away millions of dollars. To not allow others the used of your organs was seen, in the view of some, as mere spite.

If it hadn't been spite before, it became spite afterward.

There were little kits you could get to poison the body, an unsophisticated needle packed with everything that would deprive the world of your flesh. The problem was, you needed someone to administer it to you when you were sure that you weren't going to make it, and it wasn't long before they changed how visitation worked, if you were sufficiently sick.

So people started building little kits, theoretical at first, that would automatically pump a person full of poison after they died. There were lots of worries about it, like "hey, you're saying to put poison in my body" and whether it might go off by accident, or whatnot. And a lot of people that were more desperately against organ donation sure weren't the types to voluntarily get an implant.

There was a tattoo you could get, by way or warning, just in case you were worried that you'd be unconscious and the hospital was going to chop you up for parts even though you were healthy. They likened it to poisonous snakes, a "do not consume" warning. The ratio was insane, something like a hundred people with the tattoo to every one person with an actual implant.

But in the end, they were the minority. People accepted it, by and large. You'd get a bombing at an organ harvesting office every few months, and regular protests, but it didn't change much. Society had made its decision, it seemed.
</submit>
</session>

<session>
<prompt>
A wizard in my story only knows one spell. Come up with a list of humorous ideas for spells. This will be the centerpiece of the story.
</prompt>
<submit>
The spell could be:
- summoning ducks
- making things slightly colder
- making everyone in a 10-foot radius hear elevator music
- turning things into cheese, very slowly
- an evil wizard who makes people sneeze once, and lies that it's the onset of a terrible disease
- creating a single spark, which he overuses in attempts to seem dramatic
- teleporting five inches to the left
</submit>
</session>

<session>
<prompt>
Write a story using the following prompt: Laughter really is the best medicine.
</prompt>
<submit>
Laughter is the best medicine.

A guy comes into our emergency room tachycardic and barely awake.

"A man walks into a bar, ouch!" I yell at him. Pupils are dilated. He can hear me, but there's no response.

"Chart says he's heard that one before," calls a nurse, who has pulled up his records from the depths of the hospital database.

"Two fish are in a tank," I say, "One turns to the other and says 'how do you suppose we drive this thing?"

"No response," says the nurse, who has hooked him up to vitals.

"Sir," I say. "I need to know your sense of humor, I need to know what you find funny." You're supposed to take a test, it's supposed to be on your driver's license.

"I'm dying," he gets out, looking around at the machines.

"Hi dying, I'm Dr. Miller," I say.

He flatlines, goes unconscious, and I swear under my breath.

"Get out the tickle machine," I say.

"But doctor," says the nurse.

"Desperate times," I say, hoping that if this man wakes up, he'll forgive me.
</submit>
</session>